Tom Miller papers, 1852-2003 (Bulk 1950-2003)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: Publications by Tom Miller
  - Subseries 3: Books and Manuscripts
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Literature, 1902-1996, No date (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Lupi, 1985. No date (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Manabi (Pt.1), 1892-1989 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Manabi (Pt.2), No date (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Panama Hat Trail-Research Files -Manabi (P.3), No date (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Maps, No date (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Michaux, No date (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Miscellaneous, 1898-2001, No date (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Montecristi, 1998, No date (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Music, 1977-1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Olga Fisch, 1981-1990, No date (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Oriente (Pt.1), 1983-1986, No date (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Oriente (Pt.2), No date (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Quichua and Inca, No date (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Paja Taquilla (includes photograph), 1852-1998, No date (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Panama Hat History, 1900-2000, No date (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Panama Hat Name, 1994-1998, No date (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Panama Hat Sellers, U.S. (Pt.1), 1992-2001 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Panama Hat Sellers, U.S. (Pt.2), No date (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Panama Hat Statistics, No date (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Panama Hattie, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Photographs, 1983-1998, No date (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Pozo, 1978, No date (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Presidents, 1933-1998, No date (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Pujili, No date (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Puerto Lopez, No date (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Quito, 1982-1983, No date (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Reostol Hats, 1984-1985, No date (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -San Diego, 1984, No date (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -U.S Outlets, 1906-1988, No date (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Weavers, No date (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Who's Who, 1998-1999, No date (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Research Files -Raw Notes, No date (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Book Proposal, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Letter of Introduction, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Copyright Permission, 1985-1986, No date (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Manuscripts, No date (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Typeset Copy (Pt.1), 1986 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Typeset Copy (Pt.2), 1986 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Panama Hat Trail-Galley with corrections, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Panama Hat Trail-Miscellaneous Galleys, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Covers, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Introduction, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Proposal 1998, No date (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Cover and unbound galleys, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Reviews, 1986-2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Spanish Translation, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Panama Hat Trail -Page Proofs, 2001 (Box 20)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Raw Notes, No date (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Raw Notes typed, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Typed Manuscript (Pt.1), 1992 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Typed Manuscript (Pt.2), 1992 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Typed Manuscript (Pt.3), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Copy Edit Manuscript (Pt.1), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Copy Edit Manuscript (Pt.2), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Copy Edit Manuscript (Pt.3), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Copy Edit Manuscript (Pt.4), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Typeset Version (Pt.1), No date (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Typeset Version (Pt.2), No date (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Typeset Version (Pt.3), No date (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Typeset Version incomplete, No date (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Final Manuscript, Spring 1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Bound Galleys, 1992 and 1996 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Bound Galleys, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Trading with the Enemy -Cuba Documentary, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Correspondence regarding Edits 2000, No date (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink-Book Proposal, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Introduction Research Files, 1992-2000 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -General Research File, 1986-2001, No date (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Border Research File, 1977-2000 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Fast Draw Research File, No date (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Miscellaneous Research File (includes photographs) 1962-2001, No date (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -New Mexico Research File, 1994, No date (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Saguaro Research File (Pt.1), 1979-2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Saguaro Research File (Pt.2) (includes photographs), No date (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Manuscript Drafts, No date (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Edits, No date (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Final Draft, 2000 (Box 25)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Final Draft number 1 with Edits, April 4, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Final Draft number 2, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Bound Galleys (2 copies), 2000 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Public Relations, 2000-2001, No date (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink -Reviews, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Travelers' Tales -Correspondence -Authors, 2000-2001, No date (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Correspondence -Marketing, No date (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Correspondence -Travelers' Tales, 1995-2000, No date (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Contract, May 2000 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -General Information, 1997-2001, No date (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -New Yorker Cuba Issue, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Photographs, 1997-2000, No date (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Sidebars, 1962-2000, No date (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Story Ideas, No date (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Ackerman, Elise -Sailing, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Alberto, Eliseo, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Anderson, John Lee -Impressions, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Anonymous, No date (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Aschkends, Lea, No date (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Baker, Christopher, No date (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Barnet, Miguel, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Behar, Ruth -Jews, 1994, No date (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Berestein, Leslie, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Berger, Alisha -Train, No date (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Boyle, Wickham, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Brent, Bill -Sugarcane, No date (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Cantor, Judy -Music, 1994-1998 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Codrescu, Andrei, No date (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Collins, Roger, No date (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Crocker, Rebecca -Machalandia, No date (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Darling, Junaita -Tropicana, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Darling, Lynn -Prostitutes, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba-Submissions -Degelman, Charles -Impressions, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba-Submissions -Degelman, Charles -Impressions 2000 Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Dietrich, Joseph -Hemingway, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Denoes, Edmundo -Los Dispositivos, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Diedrich, Phillippe -Motocycle, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Eggers, Dave, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Eisele, Kimi -Impressions, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Evans, Paige -Experience, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Fernandez, Enrique -Impressions, 1991-1995, No date (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Fountain, Wendy -Sailing, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Freedman, Jonathan -Bicycles, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Galeano, Eduardo, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Garcia, Cristina -Personal, 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Gibson, Grameme -Santiago, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Gonzalez, Felicia -Geography Lesson, No date (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Griest, Stephanie -Sensuality, No date (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Guillearmoprieto, Alma -Music, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Head, Luis, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Heller, Peter -Kayaking Cuba, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Hoch, Danny -Hip Hop, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Hunt, Christopher, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Iyer, Pico, 1990-1994 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Jamail, Milton H., 2000 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -King, Nina -Publishers, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Koplen, Berry -Baseballs, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Kraeutler, Kirk -Tourism, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Kurianskuy, Mark -Santeria, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -John, Suki -Dancing, 1995, No date (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Letemendia, Sebastian -Impressions, No date (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba-Submissions -Lebowitz, David -Immigrant, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Linderman, Patricia -Medical, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Lopez, Antonio -Prostitute, 2000, No date (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Lowinger, Rosa -Artists KCHO, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Luxner, Larry -Jews, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba-Submissions -Matthews, Susan, No date (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba-Submissions -Mcdowell, Edwin -Travel, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -McKerrow, Richard -Youth, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -McManus, Jane, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Medina, Pablo, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Michener and Kinds, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Mona, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Mosby, Tom, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Mullen, Tom -Impressions, No data (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Oberstein, Sally -Travel Impressions, No data (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Ojito, Mirta -Native Impressions, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Paparian, William -Politics, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -O'Rourke, P.J -Impressions, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Paternostro, Silvana -Music, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Perrottet, Tony -Impressions, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Ponte, Antonio Jose, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Price, S.J., 2000 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Putman, John J. -Impressions, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Ridenour, Don -Bureaucratic, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Ripley, Peter C., 1991 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Rojo, Ricardo, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Shacochis, Bob -Tourism, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Shukman, Henry, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Smith, Scott -Havana, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Smith, Stephan -Impressions, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Snyder, Rachel L., 2000 (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Spender, Jane -Cienfuegos, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Stone, Robert, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Symmes, Patrick, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Timerman, Jacobs, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Treuhaft, Benjamin, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Treuhaft, Benjamin, No date (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Unused Articles, 1994-2000, No date (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Unused Articles, 1990 -2000, No date (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Unused Articles, 1989 - 2000 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Unused Articles, No date (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Valdes, Alisa -Family, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Vazquez, Montalban, M. -Havana, No date (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Walker, Gillian -Woman, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Watrous, Peter -Music, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Webster, Betty Ann -Travel, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -West-Duran, Allan -Mantanzas, No date (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Winkelaar, Felix -Love, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -White, Nick, No date (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -White, Randy Wayne, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Wier, Willie -Bicycle, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Submissions -Zaff, Carolyn, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Introduction, No date (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Galley, January 2001 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Typed Manuscript, February 2001 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Typed Manuscript, March 2001 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Travelers' Tales Cuba -Reviews, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Aguilar, Ricardo, 1987-1992, No date (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Aguilar, Sigfrido, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Angelou, Maya, No date (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Anzaldua, Gloria, No date (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Armenta, Jesús, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Augustin, José, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Aiken, Riley, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Aikman, Duncan, 1925 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Anaya, Rudolfo, No date (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Barlett, J.R., 1854 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Batza, Albelarado, No date (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Batchelder, Roger, 1917 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Writing on the Edge-Submissions -Beals, Carleton 1927 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Bensusan, Guy, No date (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Blackburn, Paul, 1993, No date (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Bode, Elroy, 1967-1989, No date (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Bowden, Charles, No date (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Brautigan, Richard, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Brinkley, William, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Browne, Peter Emerson, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Burroughs, Edgar Rice, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Burroughs, William, No date (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Byrd, Bobby, No date (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Camp, F.B., No date (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Campa, Author L., 1974 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Casey, Robert J., 1950 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Claremon, Neil, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Clark, Badger, No date (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Clark, Leverne, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Clarke, A.B., 1988 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Conover, Ted, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Cooke, John Byrne, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Campbell, Federico, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Corridos, No date (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Davidson, John, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Dobie, J. Frank, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Doerr, Harriet, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Emory, William H., No date (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Flores, Carlos, 1989, No date (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Fowler and Crawford, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Freedman, Jonathan, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Giib, Dagoberto, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Gomez, Guillermo, 1989, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Gonzalas, Ray 1999, No date (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Goodwin, Frank, 1944, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Gray, George W., 1926 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Hadley, Drummond, No date (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Hale, Will, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Hall, Douglas, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Haslam, Gerald, No date (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Henry, O., 1927 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Henry, Will, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Herrera-Sobek, Marie, No date (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Writing on the Edge-Submissions -Hopper, James, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Horgan, Paul, 1970,1995 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Hornaday, William, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Infante, Guillermo Cabrera, No date (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Inman, Will, 1981,1990 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Jacobs, Barbara, 1994, No date (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Jokes, 1989-1993, No date (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Kesey, Ken, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Kiefer, Warren, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Lehar, James, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Little Dog, Pat, No date (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Lopez, Barry, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Lowell, Susan, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Mathias, Fred, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Matthiessen, Peter, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Maxwell, A.E., 1988 (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -McMurty, Larry, 1966, No date (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -McWilliams, Carey, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 71)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Messick, Hank, 1987-1989 (Box 32, Folder 72)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -"Mexican American", No date (Box 32, Folder 73)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Miles, Elton, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 74)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -"Un Majodosin Licensia", No date (Box 32, Folder 75)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Mora, Pat, 1984, No date (Box 32, Folder 76)
    - Writing on the Edge-Submissions -Morris, Jan, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 77)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Muro, Amado, 1979-1982 (Box 32, Folder 78)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Nabhan, Gary Paul, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 79)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Ober, Fredrick A., 1884 (Box 32, Folder 80)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Olmsted, F.L, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 81)
    - Writing on the Edge-Submissions -Paz, Octavio, No date (Box 32, Folder 82)